

Mingyu Park

Al Researcher · Robotics Expert

291, Daehak-ro, Yuseong-gu, Daejeon, Rep. of Korea

□ (+82) 10-6484-5597 | ■m1n9yu@kaist.ac.kr | ★ https://mngupark.github.io | • mngupark | • mngupark | • mngupark | • mingyu Park

"True failure is what not trying to challenge, not what you couldn't overcome today."

Summary_

My research goal is to build **real-world** robots that can perform control tasks with human-level abilities and generalize to unseen situations using **artificial general intelligence** (AGI). I'm especially interested in developing practical methods for sequential decision-making problems. My current mission toward this goal is to devise a general method that can recover an expert policy from **static datasets** under **high-dimensional** sensory input. Formally, my research interest interleaves between **offline reinforcement learning**, **self-supervised learning**, and **foundation models**.

Education

Kwangwoon University

Seoul, S.Korea

B.S. IN ROBOTICS ENGINEERING

Mar. 2017 - Feb. 2023

• Total GPA: 4.18/4.50 Major GPA: 4.43/4.50

KAIST (Korea Advanced Institute of Science and Technology)

Daeieon, S.Korei

Mar. 2023 - Now

M.S. IN ROBOTICS PROGRAM

- Advised by Prof. Dongwhan Lee
- Total GPA: 3.94/4.30

Experience

KIST (Korea Institute of Science and Techonoloy)

Seoul, S.Kored

Undergraduate Research Assistant

Jun. 2021 - Dec. 2021

- Implemented an optimal control system of the fixed-base redundant dual-arm manipulators.
- Implemented a ROS framework to the manipulator system.
- Researched a method that can reduce the computational cost of the optimal controller for real-time control.

Seoul National University (DYROS, Dynamics Robotics Systems Lab)

Seoul, S.Kored

Undergraduate Research Intern

Jan. 2022 - Oct. 2022

- Researched a mobile robot navigation system using SLAM and extended Kalman filter.
- Researched an efficient map construction and navigation using multiple sensors on a single robot.
- Researched a whole-body controller using hierarchical quadratic programming for a mobile manipulator system.

Publications

JOURNAL

• **Park, M**., Kim, D., Oh, Y., Lee, Y. (2022). Computational Cost Reduction Method for HQP-based Hierarchical Controller for Articulated Robot. *The Journal of Korea Robotics Society*, 17(1), 16-24.

Skills_

Programming Languages Python, C, C++, HTML, CSS, JavaScript

Frameworks Robot Operating System (ROS) 1 & 2, Matlab, Docker, Tensorflow, PyTorch, Jax

Simulators Gazebo, MuJoCo, CoppeliaSim, Raisim, IsaacSim

Languages Korean, English, Japanese

Extracurricular Activity

APRIL 30, 2024 MINGYU PARK · CURRICULUM VITAE 1

BARAM (Robotics Academic Group in Kwangwoon University)

S.Korea

 CORE MEMBER
 Mar, 2020 - Dec. 2022

- Gained academic knowledge related to robotics such as computer vision and control engineering.
- Gained expertise in crafting a robot from scratch and insight to analyze complex systems.
- Obtained leadership and supervised group members serving as club director.

International Elite Summer School in Robotics & Entrepreneurship

Denmark

EMBER Aug. 2023

- Gained knowledge about advanced technologies for designing robotic systems and entrepreneurship in robotic startup companies.
- Enlarge an international network with peer students from various countries and visit leading Danish robotics companies.

Scholarships & Awards

SCHOLARSHIPS

Mar. 2017 Kwangwoon Dream , Admission Scholarship	Seoul, S.Korea
Sep. 2017 Kwangwoon Dream , Admission Scholarship	Seoul, S.Korea
Sep. 2020 Quarter tuition scholarship , Academic Excellence Scholarship	Seoul, S.Korea
Mar. 2021 Full tuition scholarship, Academic Excellence Scholarship	Seoul, S.Korea
Sep. 2021 Half tuition scholarship , Academic Excellence Scholarship	Seoul, S.Korea
Sep. 2022 Half tuition scholarship , Academic Excellence Scholarship	Seoul, S.Korea

AWARDS

Mar. 2021 Dean's List , Academic Excellence Award	Seoul, S.Korea
Sep. 2021 Dean's List , Academic Excellence Award	Seoul, S.Korea
Sep. 2022 Dean's List , Academic Excellence Award	Seoul, S.Korea